snw.media 2018-04-12

# 

                                 Slutzky & Winshman Ltd.
                                       Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the Slutzky & Winshman Ltd, dba S&W, web site. As a
user of www.snw.media, (the “Site”) you may be concerned with your privacy
and want to know what information we collect when you use our site. This
Privacy Policy contains the following:
        1.         What information is collected
        2.         How We Use the Information
        3.         Information Shared With Third Parties
        4.         Retention and Deletion of Data
        5.         Confidentiality and Security
        6.         Access
        7.         Transfer of Data Outside of Your Country
        8.         How to Contact Us
        9.         Updates to Privacy Policy
1.      What Information is Collected.
        The Site does not track your usage of the site, use cookies or collect any
        information about you unless you voluntarily complete the “Contact Us”
        section. Then it will be necessary to enter your name, email address and
        phone number. This information is deemed to be personally identifiable
        information or “PII”.
2.      How we Use the Information Collected.
        We use the PII collected in order to contact you and fulfill your request. In
        the event that we enter into a transaction with you, your contact details
        may be stored on our server during the term of our business relationship.
3.      Information Shared With Third Parties.
        We do not share your PII with third parties unless, in the unlikely event:
                  We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process, or
                   if we need to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against
                   legal claims.
S&W Privacy Policy-1                           1                                 12 APRIL 15

                  We believe in good faith it is necessary to share information in
                   order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal
                   activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to
                   the physical safety of any person or as otherwise required by law.
4.      Retention and Deletion of Data.
        We retain the information we collect as described in this Privacy Policy for
        as long as necessary to fulfil our business and/or operational purposes or
        comply with a legal request. We shall delete your PII from our systems or
        anonymize it if we deem it no longer necessary for our reasonable
        business needs.
5.      Confidentiality and Security.
        We implement measures consistent with industry standards to secure your
        PII in order to minimize the risks of damage, loss of information and
        unauthorized access or use of information. However, these measures are
        unable to provide absolute information security. Therefore, although we
        make efforts to secure your PII, we cannot guarantee, nor should there be
        any unreasonable expectation, that the Site is immune from any
        wrongdoings, malfunctions, unauthorized interceptions, or access, or other
        kinds of abuse and misuse.
6.      Access.
        You may send us a request to access the PII that we collect through the
        Site. We may require that you provide us with additional information to
        verify your identity.
7.      Transfer of Data Outside of Your Country.
        When you enter your PII on the Site, your information will be sent to our
        server which may reside in a jurisdiction other than where you are located.
        For this purpose, if you are a resident of a jurisdiction where transfer of
        your PII to another jurisdiction requires your consent, then you hereby
        provide us with your express consent to such transfer of your PII.
8.      How to Contact Us.
        If you have any questions or concerns with respect to any matter covered
        by this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by email at: info@snw.media or
        at the address set forth below:
        Slutzky & Winshman Ltd.
        1 Shenkar Street
S&W Privacy Policy-1                          2                                  12 APRIL 15

        We Work Building, 1st Floor
        Herzliya Pituach, Israel 4672501
        ATTN: Joey Winshman
9.      Updates to Privacy Policy.
        We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting updates
        on this page. We encourage you to visit and review this Privacy Policy
        frequently to stay informed. Your continued use of the Site after any
        change takes effect will indicate your acceptance of the amended Privacy
        Policy. If you do not agree with any of the amended terms, you must avoid
        any further use of the Site.
        Last Updated: April 12, 2015
S&W Privacy Policy-1                      3                             12 APRIL 15
